ILGWU. Wilbur Daniels papers, 5780/084
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series IV. Master Agreements Department, 1949-1980
  - General. K, 1968-1977 (Box 23, Folder 32)
    Kingston Dresses, Inc.; Knitted Textile Association; Koracorp Industries, Inc.
  - Kaufmann, Inc., R.and M., 1968 (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Kelita, 1969-1973 (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - Kenrose Manufacturing Company. [folder 1 of 3], 1971-1977 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Kenrose Manufacturing Company. [folder 2 of 3], 1971-1977 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Kenrose Manufacturing Company. [folder 3 of 3], 1971-1977 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Kenrose Manufacturing Company. Cutters Incentive System, 1970-1971 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Kenrose Manufacturing Company. Master Agreements and Supplements. [folder 1 of 3], 1968-1974 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Kenrose Manufacturing Company. Master Agreements and Supplements. [folder 2 of 3], 1968-1974 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Kenrose Manufacturing Company. Master Agreements and Supplements. [folder 3 of 3], 1968-1974 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Kenrose Manufacturing Company. Negotiations. [folder 1 of 4], 1963-1973 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Kenrose Manufacturing Company. Negotiations. [folder 2 of 4], 1963-1973 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Kenrose Manufacturing Company. Negotiations. [folder 3 of 4], 1963-1973 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Kenrose Manufacturing Company. Negotiations. [folder 4 of 4], 1963-1973 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Kenrose Manufacturing Company. Payroll Reports (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Kenrose Manufacturing Company. Summaries, 1971-1974 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Knitcrest Mills, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Knit-Rite Mills, 1963-1967 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Koret of California. [folder 1 of 2], 1964-1969 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Koret of California. [folder 2 of 2], 1964-1969 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - General. L, 1966-1977 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    Lawrence Manufacturing Company, Inc.; Lebanon Knitting Mill Inc.; Lincoln Garment Company
  - L'Aiglon Apparel, Inc. [folder 1 of 3], 1965-1974 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - L'Aiglon Apparel, Inc. [folder 2 of 3], 1965-1974 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - L'Aiglon Apparel, Inc. [folder 3 of 3], 1965-1974 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Leslie Fay. [folder 1 of 3], 1965-1979 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Leslie Fay. [folder 2 of 3], 1965-1979 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Leslie Fay. [folder 3 of 3], 1965-1979 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Leslie Fay. Master Agreements, 1967-1973 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Leslie Fay. Negotiations. [folder 1 of 3], 1966-1972 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Leslie Fay. Negotiations. [folder 2 of 3], 1966-1972 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Leslie Fay. Negotiations. [folder 3 of 3], 1966-1972 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Leslie Fay. Supplemental Agreements, 1970-1973 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    Branch Fashions, Inc.; Harbor Fashions, Inc.; Pennsylvania Plants
  - Leslie Fay. Divisions. Carlyle Manufacturing Corporation, 1965-1967 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Leslie Fay. Divisions. Lincolnton, 1964-1971 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Leslie Fay. Divisions. Personal Sportswear. [folder 1 of 2] (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Leslie Fay. Divisions. Personal Sportswear. [folder 2 of 2] (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Lilli Ann, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Lily Lynn Inc., 1966 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Little Lisa. Precious Girl, 1968-1970 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Lortogs. International Outerwear, Inc. [folder 1 of 3], 1964-1967 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Lortogs. International Outerwear, Inc. [folder 2 of 3], 1964-1967 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Lortogs. International Outerwear, Inc. [folder 3 of 3], 1964-1967 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - General. M, 1975-1978 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    Mackintosh (of Girltown); Mercer Dress Manufacturing Company; Merle Hinson; Monsanto Company; Morris Manufacturing
  - Maidenform, Inc. [folder 1 of 3], 1965-1978 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Maidenform, Inc. [folder 2 of 3], 1965-1978 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Maidenform, Inc. [folder 3 of 3], 1965-1978 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Maidenform, Inc. Arbitration, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Maidenform, Inc. Contract Proposals, 1967-1971 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Maidenform, Inc. Cost of Living Arbitration, 1967-1971 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Maidenform, Inc. Edison Plant, 1968-1975 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Maidenform, Inc. Letter Agreement. (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Maidenform, Inc. Master Agreement, 1966-1969 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Maidenform, Inc. Mediation Notices, 1971-1975 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Maidenform, Inc. Negotiations. [folder 1 of 4], 1966-1977 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Maidenform, Inc. Negotiations. [folder 2 of 4], 1966-1977 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Maidenform, Inc. Negotiations. [folder 3 of 4], 1966-1977 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Maidenform, Inc. Negotiations. [folder 4 of 4], 1966-1977 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Maidenform, Inc. Puerto Rico Plant, 1972-1973 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Maidenform, Inc. Sample Room, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Maidenform, Inc. Severance Payments: E.J. Sportswear, 1965-1971 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Maidenform, Inc. West Virginia, 1957-1966 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Maidenform, Inc. Majestic Specialties, Inc. [folder 1 of 4], 1959-1972 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Maidenform, Inc. Majestic Specialties, Inc. [folder 2 of 4], 1959-1972 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Maidenform, Inc. Majestic Specialties, Inc. [folder 3 of 4], 1959-1972 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Maidenform, Inc. Majestic Specialties, Inc. [folder 4 of 4], 1959-1972 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Majestic Specialities, Inc. Bobbi Rogers, 1965-1967 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Majestic Specialties, Inc. Master Agreement, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Majestic Specialties, Inc. Negotiations, 1967-1970 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Malcolm Starr, Inc., 1970 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Manhattan Industries, Inc., 1968-1970 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Manpower Advisory Committee, 1967-1969 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Marlboro Classics, 1969-1970 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    affiliate of Puritan Fashions Corporation
  - Marlene Industries, 1969 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Marshalla Corporation, 1969 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 1968 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Master Agreement Analyses, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Match Mates, Inc., 1967 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - May Lingerie, Inc., 1967 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Mayflower Dress Corporation, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Mercer Clothing Manufacturing Company, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Michael Industries, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Midwest Region Department, 1966-1972 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Mode O'Day, 1950-1979 (Box 26, Folder 26-32)
  - Mode O'Day. Checks, 1967-1972 (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - Mode O'Day. Contracts. [folder 1 of 2], 1958-1964 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Mode O'Day. Contracts. [folder 2 of 2], 1958-1964 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Mode O'Day. National Agreements. [folder 1 of 6], 1957-1970 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Mode O'Day. National Agreements. [folder 2 of 6], 1957-1970 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Mode O'Day. National Agreements. [folder 3 of 6], 1957-1970 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Mode O'Day. National Agreements. [folder 4 of 6], 1957-1970 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Mode O'Day. National Agreements. [folder 5 of 6], 1957-1970 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Mode O'Day. National Agreements. [folder 6 of 6 ], 1957-1970 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Mode O'Day. Negotiations. [folder 1 of 5], 1963-1973 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    includes Founders, Inc.
  - Mode O'Day. Negotiations. [folder 2 of 5], 1963-1973 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Mode O'Day. Negotiations. [folder 3 of 5], 1963-1973 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Mode O'Day. Negotiations. [folder 4 of 5], 1963-1973 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Mode O'Day. Negotiations. [folder 5 of 5], 1963-1973 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Mode O'Day. Sharing Plan, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Mode O'Day. Strike Benefits (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - General. N, 1976-1978 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    National Handbag Association; National Skirt and Sportswear Association; New England Region; New York Sportswear Exchange
  - National Labor Relations Board, 1967-1979 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Negotiations. [folder 1 of 2], 1978-1979 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Negotiations. [folder 2 of 2], 1978-1979 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - New York Cloak Joint Board, 1968-1972 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - New York Dress Joint Board, 1967-1976 (Box 28, Folder 1-9)
  - Northeast Department.[folder 1 of 5], 1966-1977 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Northeast Department. [folder 2 of 5], 1966-1977 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Northeast Department. [folder 3 of 5], 1966-1977 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Northeast Department. [folder 4 of 5], 1966-1977 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Northeast Department. [folder 5 of 5], 1966-1977 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - General. O, 1965 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    Originala, Inc.
  - Ohio. Kentucky region, 1968-1972 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - General. P, 1974-1978 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    Personal and Breckenridge; Perfection; Piece Workers
  - Philadelphia Dress Joint Board, 1968-1972 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Puerto Rico, 1965-1972 (Box 29, Folder 3-10)
  - Puerto Rico. Blairmoor, 1969-1972 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Puritan Fashions Corporation. [folder 1 of 3], 1963-1972 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Puritan Fashions Corporation. [folder 2 of 3], 1963-1972 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Puritan Fashions Corporation. [folder 3 of 3], 1963-1972 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Puritan Fashions Corporation. Master and Supplemental Agreements. [folder 1 of 4], 1967-1973 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    includes supplemental agreement for: Puritan Skirt and Dress Corporation; Moody Dress Corporation; Jay Dress Corporation; Paul Modes Inc.; Sherry Gail Inc.; Claire Tiffany Inc.; Domani Knits; Chatham Dress Corporation; Hampton Apparel Company; Walterboro Dress Corporation
  - Puritan Fashions Corporation. Master and Supplemental Agreements. [folder 2 of 4], 1967-1973 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Puritan Fashions Corporation. Master and Supplemental Agreements. [folder 3 of 4], 1967-1973 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Puritan Fashions Corporation. Master and Supplemental Agreements. [folder 4 of 4], 1967-1973 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Puritan Fashions Corporation. Negotiations. [folder 1 of 3], 1966-1977 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Puritan Fashions Corporation. Negotiations. [folder 2 of 3], 1966-1977 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Puritan Fashions Corporation. Negotiations. [folder 3 of 3], 1966-1977 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - General. R, 1966-1974 (Box 29, Folder 22)
    Rappahanock Sportswear Company, Inc.; Rosenau Brothers
  - Fred Rothschild of California, 1968-1970 (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Russ Togs. [folder 1 of 5], 1966-1970 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Russ Togs. [folder 2 of 5], 1966-1970 (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Russ Togs. [folder 3 of 5], 1966-1970 (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - Russ Togs. [folder 4 of 5], 1966-1970 (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - Russ Togs. [folder 5 of 5], 1966-1970 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Russ Togs. Juniorette, 1966-1972 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - General. S, 1966-1976 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    St. Louis Associated Garment Industries; Solon reorganization - Ohio region; Seven Over Seven Corporation; Stanbury Corporation; Susan Thomas
  - S and S Manufacturing Company, Inc., 1967 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Sample Room Contracts. Master Agreement Firms, 1949-1965 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - San Francisco Joint Board. [folder 1 of 2], 1964-1976 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - San Francisco Joint Board. [folder 2 of 2], 1964-1976 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Savon Cleaners, 1966-1969 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Sears Roebuck and Company, 1964-1966 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Scottex Corporation, 1971-1972 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Segal, Martin E. Company, 1966-1969 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Ship n'Shore, Inc., 1965-1968 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Sirr Knit, 1971-1972 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Slate Belt Apparel, 1964-1967 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Smoler Brothers, 1967-1970 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Southeast Region. [folder 1 of 6], 1962-1972 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Southeast Region. [folder 2 of 6], 1962-1972 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Southeast Region. [folder 3 of 6], 1962-1972 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Southeast Region. [folder 4 of 6], 1962-1972 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Southeast Region. [folder 5 of 6], 1962-1972 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Southeast Region. [folder 6 of 6], 1962-1972 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Spatz Brothers, Inc., 1969 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Spirite Industries, 1970-1972 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - Thomas Holmes Corporation, 1968-1969 (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - Trophy Fashions, Inc., 1968-1972 (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - General. U, 1965-1966 (Box 30, Folder 26)
    US Industries, Inc.
  - Upper South Department. [folder 1 of 5], 1961-1977 (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - Upper South Department. [folder 2 of 5], 1961-1977 (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - Upper South Department. [folder 3 of 5], 1961-1977 (Box 30, Folder 29)
  - Upper South Department. [folder 4 of 5], 1961-1977 (Box 30, Folder 30)
  - Upper South Department. [folder 5 of 5], 1961-1977 (Box 30, Folder 31)
  - General. V, 1977-1978 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Villager Industries, Inc., 1960-1978 (Box 31, Folder 2-8)
  - General. W, 1976-1978 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    Weather Downs; Wilroy, Inc.; Wintex Knitting Mill
  - Wentworth Manufacturing Company, 1966-1969 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Westbury Fashions, Inc. [folder 1 of 5], 1960-1978 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Westbury Fashions, Inc. [folder 2 of 5], 1960-1978 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Westbury Fashions, Inc. [folder 3 of 5], 1960-1978 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Westbury Fashions, Inc. [folder 4 of 5], 1960-1978 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Westbury Fashions, Inc. [folder 5 of 5], 1960-1978 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Westway Project, 1978 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Master Agreement Department Files. Multi Company Documents. [folder 1 of 2], 1965-1979 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Master Agreement Department Files. Multi Company Documents. [folder 1 of 2], 1965-1979 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Master Agreement Department Files. Miscellaneous. [folder 1 of 2], 1964-1979 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Master Agreement Department Files. Miscellaneous. [folder 1 of 2], 1964-1979 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Master Agreement Department Files. Miscellaneous Financial Revolving Fund. [folder 1 of 3], 1956- 1978 (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Master Agreement Department Files. Miscellaneous Financial Revolving Fund. [folder 2 of 3], 1956- 1978 (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - Master Agreement Department Files. Miscellaneous Financial Revolving Fund. [folder 3 of 3], 1956- 1978 (Box 31, Folder 23)
- Series V. Personal
  - Personal. Miscellaneous, 1944-1979 (Box 32, Folder 1-13)
    includes novels